Oh, hi.
Hey.
So, uh, what's the big news
you had us rush
all the way over here for?
Okay, our news...
my company has asked me
to head up our office
in Tulsa.
So, as of Monday,
I'm being officially relocated.
What?
Monday?
Oh, my God.
Well, how long do
you have to go for?
Well, they said it could be
up to a year.
A year?
Oh, my God.
Do you have to go?
Well, I kind of
have to, don't I?
'Cause of this stupid thing.
There's nothing like the support
of your loving wife, huh?
Wait a minute, wait...
you can't go to Tulsa.
Maybe you forgot,
but we have tickets
to the Jets game next week.
Well, I'm sorry, buddy
but I don't think
I'm going to be
able to make it.
W-W-We were going to go
see the Jets.
You-You can't go.
I mean, you're the glue
that holds this group together.
Really?
Not you.
God, I can't believe
you guys are moving.
I call their apartment!
Oh, no.
No.
Yeah!
Come on.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Here you go, Rach.
Oh, thank you, Joey.
Oh, you know what?
I'm not even sure
I can have caffeine.
I went through this
with Ben and Carol.
One cup of coffee
won't affect your milk.
Yeah, well, just to be sure,
I'm going to call Dr. Wiener.
( chuckling )
Every time?
Uh-huh.
Rach, you don't
have to call him
whenever you have
a little question, okay?
Trust me. I know this.
All right, I trust you.
Rachel, I can see you dialing.
I don't understand why...
Shh, I'm on the phone.
Dr. Wiener?
( chuckles )
It's so weird seeing Ross
and Rachel with a baby.
It's just so grown up.
I know, yeah.
I feel like
we're all growing up.
Uh-huh.
A person named Wiener.
God that kills me.
Look at you all grown up.
Yeah, well, actually--
actually, you know what?
I am.
You know...
Yeah.
Yeah, well,
that whole thing with Rachel
made me realize
that maybe I'm ready
for a more serious
relationship, you know?
Like, I'd like to meet a nice,
mature, commitment-minded lady.
And looks aren't important as...
Nah, she's got to be hot.
Well, you know, I
might know somebody.
Hey, how about
you setting me
up with someone
and we double-date?
I can do that.
Yeah, how's Friday?
Done.
All right.
Oh, good, really?
Yeah.
Okay, let's see...
( little-girl giggle )
All right... um...
ooh, you know who's great?
Sandy Poopack.
( chuckles )
Poo-pack.
Yeah, all right.
Well, that rules
out Lana Titwiller.
( laughing )
Hey.
I've got good news.
You got out
of the whole Tulsa thing?
Okay, I have news.
You don't have to move to Tulsa.
You can stay here
and keep your job.
That's great. How?
Well, my boss and I
worked out a deal
where I only have to be
in Tulsa four days a week.
So, the other three
I can be here with you.
So, you're going to be gone
four days a week?
No.
I'm sorry, are you just
used to saying that?
No. I can't be away
from you for that long.
Really?
Yeah, you're my husband.
I'm not going to live in
a different state than you
for 208 days out of the year.
That's fast math.
We could use you in Tulsa.
Honey, thanks for trying
to figure out a way
but if you're
going to Tulsa
I want to go with you.
Hey, you said that
without gagging.
I know.
Well, excuse me?
Oh, yeah?
Well, up yours, too.
Who the hell was that?
Dr. Wiener.
Rach, you can't call people
at 3:00 in the morning.
You know what?
You sound just like his wife.
Was there anything
even wrong with Emma?
Yes, of course
there is.
Okay, I'm not insane.
Well, what was it?
Hiccups.
Rach, I told you,
you can't call him
every time any little thing
comes up.
Yeah, well, not anymore I can't.
He fired us.
God, what are we
going to do?
We have to find
a pediatrician.
Wait, wait, wait.
Monica said that when you guys
were growing up
you really liked
your doctor.
What was his name?
Dr. Gettleman?
Uh, yeah, no, I don't...
I don't think
that's a good idea.
In fact I think he's--
I think he's dead.
Ach, why does everything
happen to me?
Look, Rach, I promise
first thing tomorrow
we'll find another doctor
but I got to get up early
and I'm not feeling
all that well.
What? Wh-Wh-What
you're not feeling well?
What do you have?
Is it rubella?
Because don't go near Emma,
she has not had that shot.
You know, come to think of it,
it does feel rubella-like.
Weeennneeer!
Wiener!
Wiener, Wiener, Wiener...
Rachel!
Great. Now he's going to know
it was me.
Hey.
So, how is this for our
big double-date tonight?
Oh, my God.
Ooh, great.
Just the reaction
I was hoping for.
Yeah, yes, so you, uh,
you found someone for me?
You didn't forget?
Of course not.
And you are going
to love Mary Ellen.
She's really smart and
cute and funny and...
I can't tell you
how I know this
but she is not opposed
to threesomes.
Oh, really?
( mumbles )
Yeah.
So, tell me something
about my guy.
No.
Come on, give me something.
What's his name?
Mike.
Mike?
Yeah.
Okay. What's his last name?
Damn it, is there no mystery
left in romance anymore?
All right, we'll
see you and Mike
at the restaurant
in couple of hours.
Okay. All right, great.
All right. Yeah.
See you. Bye-bye.
Why did I have to say Mike?
I don't know a Mike.
Why couldn't I have said...
There's no guys in there.
Oh, it's impossible
to find a good doctor.
I mean, how do you know
the good ones from the ones
who are going to push their
penis against your knee?
Excuse me?
I know what she's talking about.
Uh, yeah.
Well, we've got to find
a new pediatrician.
Ross was getting sick last night
and I think Emma
may have caught it.
Why don't you go see
Dr. Gettleman?
Ross said he died.
He didn't die.
I just saw his daughter
last week.
Said he was fine.
Her, on the other hand,
botched Botox.
Oh, great.
Well, then I'm going to take
Emma to see him.
I wonder why Ross
said that he died?
Oh, maybe he was
getting him confused
with his childhood therapist.
He saw a therapist?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, he used to have
this recurring nightmare.
Just really freaked him out.
Why? What was it?
That I was going to eat him.
Mike!
Yeah?
Okay.
MIKE:
I got to tell you
I can't believe
I'm doing this with you.
Although, yeah, I did just get
out of a nine-year relationship.
So, I guess I should be
open to taking some risks.
Everything's going to be fine.
Just follow my lead, okay?
All you have to do is
pretend to be Mike.
I am Mike.
That a boy.
Okay, here they come.
Hi, I'm Phoebe.
Hey, Phoebe, Mike.
Nice to meet you.
Joey, this is
Mary Ellen Jenkins.
So, Mike, how do you and Joey
know each other anyway?
How do I and Joey
know each other? Wow.
If I had a nickel for every time
somebody's asked me that.
( laughing )
From-from school.
Yeah, we met in college.
I mean high school.
Wow, you guys go
way back, then.
So, what are you
up to these days?
Well, I'm a lawyer.
Mike, Attorney-at-Law.
Actually, I just gave up
my practice.
What?
That's the kind of thing
you usually run by me.
Well, I always wanted
to play piano professionally
and I figured if I don't
do this now I never will.
Wow, that's great.
I like that better
than the lawyer thing. So...
Which is why I waited until
now to introduce you to Mike.
I thought you thought
he was still a lawyer?
No, no, no.
That's not what I meant.
Let's-let's get you a cocktail.
( snaps his fingers )
Hey.
What are you doing?
Looking for restaurant jobs
for you in Tulsa.
Oh, that's so sweet.
Did you find anything?
Slim Pickins'.
Nothing, huh?
No. Slim Pickins'.
It's a barbecue joint.
They're looking for a cook.
Actually "cook" may be
a bit of a stretch.
They're looking for somebody
to shovel mesquite.
Slim Pickins'.
That is so cheesy.
So Cheesy also
has an opening.
Well, honey, that's okay.
I actually know
this woman, Nancy
who's a-- she's
a restaurant biz headhunter.
Maybe she'll
know something.
Can I just say how much I
appreciate you coming with me.
When we get to Tulsa
I am taking you for a
great dinner at Slim Pickins'.
So Cheesy?
Whole Hog?
It's going to be tough
to keep kosher in Tulsa?
Hi, Nancy?
Hi, it's Monica Geller.
I'm good.
Listen, I'm looking for a job
in Tulsa.
Well, my husband's
been relocated.
Because I love him.
No, no, I don't want a job
in New York.
Javu's looking?
Oh, my God.
He asked for me personally?
Oh, my God!
Oh, wow, this is really,
really flattering.
But, um, I'm moving to Tulsa.
Yeah, so, just if you
would tell Javu...
I'll take it!
Hi, my name's
Rachel Green.
I have an appointment for Emma.
Dr. Gettleman is finishing up
with a patient.
He should be out shortly.
Okay, thank you.
I think you just have a cold.
It's definitely not strep.
Thanks, doctor.
Would you like
a lollipop?
Even have to ask?
He is alive!
You know,
it's so surprising
that you and Joey
have known each
other for so long
and I've never
heard about you.
Oh, that's... that's because
we had a bit of a falling out.
Mike... hit my mom
with a car.
No, I didn't.
It's okay, Mike.
I have forgiven you.
And now we're friends again,
and everything's great.
Wait. Is your mom okay?
Please, we're trying
to have a conversation.
Wow, you're a lot nicer
on Days of Our Lives.
Days of Our Lives.
That's why you look
so familiar.
What?
Do you not know
each other?
( chuckling )
Of course we do.
Mike is playing a game
that we used to play
in high school.
Yeah, where we pretend
we don't know each other.
We played all kinds of games.
Hey, you remember that one
where I punch you in the face
for not being cool?
Mike, let me
ask you something.
How many sisters
does Joey have?
Six.
What are you doing?
I said seven!
Oh!
Joey, why did you set me up
with a stranger?
Because I... I forgot
about our date.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
And just to be clear
I didn't hit his mother
with a car.
You are unbelievable.
I spent so much time
finding the perfect
girl for you, you know?
Mary Ellen is really
smart and cute and loose.
Hey!
Oh, who are you kidding?
You just find some guy
off the street for me?
God, this is humiliating.
Phoebe, I'm
so sorry.
Hey, look, if you don't
like this guy
I can find you a better one.
Mike? Mike?
I'm out of here.
It was nice
meeting you.
You're leaving,
too?
I'll stay if you can
tell me my name.
Have a good night.
Honey, we're
leaving tomorrow
and you've still got
a lot of packing to do.
You're right.
Maybe I shouldn't go.
What?
Um... So Nancy told me about
this... this job
at this great restaurant,
Javu.
But it's just a little
outside of Tulsa.
Well, how far outside?
Manhattan.
And, uh, you're
thinking of taking it?
So, before you said
that being with me
was more important
than any job
but I guess now it's
old job... me... new job.
I'm going to miss this hand.
Okay, I know this
is a lot to ask
but, oh, my God, Chandler
this is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity.
What happened to
"you can't live without me
four days a week"?
Well, if you really
think about it
I mean four days
is just not that long.
I mean...
I see you Monday
before you go to work
and then I see you
Thursday when you get back
and I always work late
on Tuesdays
so really if you
think about it...
it's really just one day.
And, um, if we can't
make it one day
we got real problems,
my friend.
I think you should take the job.
Really?
Yeah. I know it must be
important to you
when you start chattering
like a monkey.
That's the nicest thing
anybody's ever said to me.
Hey.
How was the pediatrician?
Oh, I really
liked him.
Yeah, yeah, it was really,
really, really good.
You promised you wouldn't
say anything.
I know.
Ross still sees
his pediatrician!
I don't care.
Are you serious?
You still see
Dr. Gettleman?
He is a brilliant
diagnostician.
Diagnostician or...
boo-boo fixer?
Ross, seriously, you've got
to go to an appropriate doctor.
Why? Why?
I know it's a little weird
but, hey, he is a great doctor,
okay?
He knows my medical history
and every time I go in there
he makes a big deal.
"Oh, look,
it's my favorite patient."
Does he say that
before he sticks his thermometer
in your tushie?
Hey, I seem to remember
someone bringing his
security blanket to college.
That was not
a security blanket.
That was a wall hanging.
It didn't spend much time
on the wall!
Oh, excuse me.
Hi.
I was hoping to run into you.
Uh, can we talk?
Sure.
I'm sorry.
Really, I'm
so embarrassed.
Really, I'm a pretty nice guy.
Just ask my parole officer.
Apparently, I'm not a funny guy.
Well, why did you
go along with it?
Because I was told
that I'd get a free dinner.
Which I didn't.
And that I'd meet
a pretty girl.
Which I did.
That's true.
Well... is anything
you told me about
yourself true?
My name is Mike.
And I do play piano.
Oh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
Prove it.
There isn't a piano here.
That wouldn't stand in the way
of a true pianist.
Okay.
You are really good.
Wow.
I'm... I play a little
guitar myself.
Really?
Uh-huh.
That's great.
Yeah.
What kind of music
do you play?
Well, um... like acoustic
folksy stuff, you know.
But right now I'm working
on a couple Iron Maiden covers.
Do you think
that maybe...
sometime I could...?
It's okay.
Go ahead, ask me out.
Okay.
You think maybe sometime
I could take you out?
Oh, you just caught me
off guard.
Yes. That would
be nice, yeah.
Look at this--
my two best friends.
Excuse me.
I don't mean
to be a jerk
but the baby with
the rash came in after me.
The doctor will be
right with you, sir.
Mommy, I can't
find Waldo.
What? The circus?
He's behind the elephant.
Wow. So your child's
a big fan
of the Waldo books, too?
Yeah, that's how I know.
I'm Ross, by the way.
Hi. I'm Sally.
Hi.
So, no ring.
Can I assume you're also
a single parent?
I am a single parent.
It's hard, isn't it?
There's almost no time
for a social life.
I mean, where are you going
to meet someone?
Well, uh... let's say,
I don't know
you met someone
in the...
pediatrician's office.
Rossie, we're ready for you.
Um, yeah.
Come on, Ross Jr.
It's time to go in.
Mommy, what's wrong
with that man?
Hey, I helped you find Waldo!
( door opening )
Oh, good, you haven't left yet.
Where have you been?
I got held up
at Dr. Gettleman's office.
Uh, there was some guy
that, uh...
freaked everybody out.
Well, you got here
just in time.
I really have to go, buddy.
Oh, man.
Honey, promise to call
me when you land?
Of course
I will call you.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Okay, whoa, whoa.
whoa, whoa.
Whoa, watch
the tongue, people.
We got a baby over here.
Bye, Chandler.
Oh, bye.
Bye, honey.
Bye.
What's the matter, Joe?
I'm mad at you
for leaving.
You're nothing but
a big leaver.
A big leaver with
a stupid suitcase.
Any chance you're trying
to pick a fight
to make all of this easier?
Oh, dude, you see
right through me.
Okay, well, bye, Mon...
Bye, Ross, Rachel...
Bye, Emma...
Okay, bye-bye.
Have a good trip.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Chandler...
Wait.
It goes, old job...
new job...
and you.
This is just something
I have to do.
I know.
I love you so much.
I know that, too.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Don't worry.
I'll be back before you know it.
Yes, it will be the same.
Because I know, that's how.
I promise.
You double promise?
Well, call me
when you land.
Can I talk now?
Okay, bye.
Joey?!
He had to board.